{
    "id": "f96d250480244cbeb460da0cd0105c01",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I did not beat her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "She is not beaten by me.",
                "She has not beaten by me.",
                "She was not beaten by me."
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I will never forget this experience.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "This experience is not forgotten by me.",
                "This experience would never be forgotten by me.",
                "This experience will never be forgotten by me."
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Mother made a cake yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "A cake made by mother yesterday.",
                "A cake is made by mother yesterday.",
                "A cake was made by mother yesterday."
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy teased the girl.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "The girl was teased by the boy.",
                "The girl had teased by the boy."
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Did she do her duty?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Was she done her duty?",
                "Was her duty done by her?",
                "Had her duty done by her?"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The tiger was chasing the deer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "The deer was chased by the tiger.",
                "The deer was being chased by the tiger.",
                "The deer had chased by the tiger."
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She has written a novel.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "A novel has written by her.",
                "A novel has been written  by her.",
                "A novel had written by her."
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She has learned her lessons.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Her lessons has learned by her.",
                "Her lessons have been learned by her.",
                "Her lessons had been learned by her."
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you finished the report?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Has the report finished by you?",
                "Has the report been finished by you?",
                "Had the report been finished by you?"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The police have caught the thief.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "The thief has been caught by the police.",
                "The thief was caught by the police.",
                "The thief had been caught by the police."
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}